

Contacto

- jcdeveloped@gmail.com
- 0412-8025609 412-1093622
- https://codefazt.github.io/curriculum-vite
- https://www.youtube.com/@johancarmino6116
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/johan-carmino-3b8775201/

INTERESTS

- DMaking videos about pentesting and programming techniques.
- Solving machines on sites like: tryhackme.com, vulnhub, dockerslab, etc.

Skills

- Python (Kivy, DJango, PySpark, Flask, PyQT5)
- C# (.NetCore, Razor, Forms, MVC5)
- JavaScript: (Vanilla, JQuery, Angular.js, React.js, Vue.js)
- Otros: Go, PHP, JAVA
- Git, Docker, kubernetes, Pm2, Rabbit, Ngnix, Apache, Pentaho ETL, Tibco, Spark
- DB: SQLServer, Postgres, Redshift, Oracle, MySQL, SQLite, MongoDB, FireBase
- Accounting, administration and finance: ERP (Odoo, Erpnext, Profit)
- · Bash Scripting
- Al & Machine Learning: Large Language Models (LLMs), computer vision, natural language processing (NLP), etc.
- Automation: n8n, Zapier, Power Automate, etc.

GITHUB

• https://github.com/codefazt

JOHAN CARMINO

FULL STACK DEVELOPER | DEVOPS | CYBERSECURITY

I am a developer passionate about innovation and development, always keeping up with new market technologies.

I specialize in development architecture, including networks, infrastructure, and especially, information security.

I perform red team and blue team tests on the applications I develop to improve the experience of the delivered products. I have over 7 years of experience in various programming languages such as C#, Golang, Java, JavaScript, PHP, and Python, among others.

Work experience

O PROGRAMMER ANALYST (APP-ACCOUNTING - ERP)

EXLCE-Soluciones biométricas - Biopago | 2022 - Present

Creation of an internal system (ERP) for accounting and finance management, employee payroll, logistics of product and service (purchasesales). Framework used -> (Frappe with ERPNEXT), Python, JavaScript, Docker containers.

Conducted cybersecurity audits of web applications including Biopagobdv, ErpNext, and Saime.

Performed comprehensive security assessments using a variety of techniques such as port scanning, directory and subdomain fuzzing, sensitive information enumeration, and vulnerability analysis by verifying application versions and checking for known CVEs.

WEB PROGRAMMER ANALYST

MGI-Acussys | 2019 - 2022

Full Stack web developer in Golang, C#.NetCore, JavaScript with Vue. (Creation of Factory model app).

ANALYST PROGRAMMER MENTION PYTHON

Vettica - Colombia| January 2021 - September 2021

Process and manage data between different databases with Python script creations, management, manipulation of Big Data with Spark in PySpark, Panda, and Pentaho ETL.

WEB PROGRAMMER ANALYST

Darien Technology - Panama | 2021

Creation of Web systems with Angular.js, Django, different Databases like (Postgres, Redshift, Mysql, Server setups and version control (Git) and container management with Docker).

Education

ING. MECANICA

U.P.T.N.M Ludovico Silva | 2013 - 2018

ING SISTEMA

Courses web and channels: (Platzi, PildorasInformaticas, CodeFazt, Udemy, hack4u.io, CCNA, NetworkChuck, others)